Karim Abdelhalim

Web & Mobile application react developer

SUMMARY

I am a passionate self-taught front-end developer. I love coding creative UIs and bringing designs to life with clean, efficient code. My expertise includes building responsive and user-friendly websites and applications, constantly learning and adapting to new technologies and trends to deliver the best digital experiences.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Front-end Developer at MedC

OCT 2023 - 2024

Collaborated with a skilled team to deliver a medical educational app, focusing on enhancing the user interface and experience.

- Development of Mobile application UI
- Development of website UI
- Links: website mobile app

Front-end Developer at Ringfill

DEC 2023 - 2024

Contributed to both frontend and backend development for various tasks such as:

- Development of Mobile application UI
- Enhancements on website
- Links: website mobile app

COURSEES & TRAININGS

DEPI | React Development

April 2024 - OCT2024

Ministry of communications Information, Egypt

- Cloud computing | web development (HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript)
- Front-end development (React.js, Tailwind CSS)
- Back-end development (node.js, Express.js, MongoDB)
- Soft Skills
- Business English

Front-end Development

2023

Almenor Platform

- Web development using HTML5 & CSS3
- Mastering CSS flex, CSS Grid & CSS Animation
- JavaScript for expert levels
- Git & GitHub

PROJECTS

Anubis-ui

- Description: A React based ui library that contains a growing collection of reusable components.
- Technologies: Next.js, TypeScript, tailwind CSS, three.js, framer motion, gsap
- Links: Web Page

UnityCare hospital

- Description: This platform was developed to provide a comprehensive solution for healthcare services. It allows patients to easily book appointments, access information about doctors and specialties, and stay informed with the latest medical news.
- Technologies: Next.js, TypeScript, tailwind CSS, Shadcn UI, node.js, MongoDB
- Links: GitHub Web Page

CONTACTS

Phone: (+20) 102 309 6263 **Address**: Egypt, Cairo

Email: Karimoda66@gmail.com

LINKS

- LinkedIn
- GitHub
- Portfolio

EDUCATION

ASU Mechanical engineering (Mechatronic department)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programing Languages

- HTML
- Type Script
- CSS
- PythonC++
- Java Scripts

Front-end

- React.js
- Next.js
- Shadcn UI
- React Native

Back-end

- Node.js
- Express.js
- MongoDB
- Prisma

Version Control

• Git

GitHub

Design/Prototyping

• Figma

LANGUAGES

Arabic (Native)

English